I'm actually in Maryland manatee who
really symbolizes service to others in
all of her adventures I can't I need to
see the fur hurry up all right
that being said I was so taken by our
conversation that we were able to have
ahead of this event to do those honors
is John O'Brien I'd like to call him up
here John O'Brien's a member of the
Irish community who really does a lot
for everyone here in Northeast Ohio
there you are sir we have a good chance
to talk beforehand my goodness he's the
co-founder publisher and editor of the
Ohio irish-american news the Ohio large
American news is a monthly news magazine
it's got a lot of reach because we have
a lot of proud Irish people in Northeast
Ohio hundred seventy six thousand in
Cuyahoga County alone almost half a
million in Greater Cleveland and over a
million in the great state of Ohio it's
a strong group of people a crowded group
of people
John's around them he's also I guess you
could say legacy his father was also
very involved too he was the president
of the West Side Irish and there have
been 12 for 20 years
Jarnell takes that man assumes that John
O'Brien interesting Maryland man
[Applause]
right good
congratulations so she's right across
the 30 issues in 30 months but certainly
the blessing of have the Maryland is my
life as a friend award the 30 years my
mind to open presents
Hawaiian's voice she's a leader who's
executive I continue to seek out and
asked her advice now but never with the
news danger they say you can be touched
by the company that you keep
I had three older systems much older
sisters and my mind really developing
that voice for me she's a leader whose
perspective is wise
she'd been there succeed as she's done
it I've always found because of those
three sisters and the kind every great
woman is another great woman or maybe
more and Maryland's team - when I call
them that are out there take a little
bit over the table over there they got
the great women behind the great woman
and where we're going
or not there there you really have a
bridge to the friendship group people
feels you in a row and they're all the
that's all de-identified I believe
that's all that sound about us it's
about us together they say that the
greatest of a person can do ecology
mentioned by the willingness to be kind
I believe that there are no mountain
high in this world and to say that
someone hasn't challenged soul
they care more for others that we do
from themselves it's a harder path at
the core of the road to be kind as
opposed to being yourself you're retired
you're stretched distracted and you snap
out they don't help you just want to go
home and see season a review of games of
Thrones and I can understand go first
but in other works our goals in life
inside two hours I bet he could life
teaches us what really matters when
people are first my people matter first
we don't write our own magazine it
writes itself with absolute vision
blasting your knightress appointment or
a community of most important is elected
in the human the enforcement Michael
goes around us between generous soul I'm
sure you've read Maryland's Bible in the
book there I won't because of that but
if you've seen her in person
the read that versity called it and the
willingness to answer the call so
Marilyn doesn't sit there and say oh I
wish something would stop us Marilyn
Stanton says I will stop us and she gets
involved whether it be getting Church of
Mobile in st. Patrick's I'm glad you
ever tried or helping the festivals or
how they would use paper it doesn't
matter
rebel says I will help she found the
battle herself and leads away that's
advice I can give you is don't get her
away
she's nice she's never ever weak whole
thing doesn't set out to build their own
Bible they recognize the tremendous gift
we have in life that they are given each
day exchanging one day if I'd like for
that gift for something hopefully
worthwhile it's a fair trade for that
gives me the day the week of your life
they set out to make the world a better
place for their being there that's all
[Applause]
I would like to first thank Debbie and
Dan Hanson and their mom for all and all
those that are involved in the Cleveland
International Hall of Fame
congratulations to my fellow inductees
and thank you John for those kind words
I'm very humbled and honored to receive
this award and I have to thank my
parents because they've instilled in me
my love of my faith my family my
friendships my heritage and my country
an award like this you did not get the
loan it's all those people that have
been on your journey with you so at this
time if I could ask my family and my
friends to please stand
[Applause]
thank you for your love and support I
love my Irish heritage
they love sharing its rich history and
culture as many others but I'm a better
person because of the friendships that I
have developed whether it's in my own
community or with a great group of
nurses that I've met over 38 years ago
each one of these people have shared
their own ethnic heritage with me as
made me a better person
I love Cleveland and what makes
Cleveland special is that we've had many
immigrants make this area their home
they brought their culture and their
traditions and a main Cleveland treasure
when I look at this class and I look
back at those who have gone before us
starting with the first class they all
brought to mind a quote that I heard
from Pope John Paul the second when he
visited I really in 1979
I changed one word and added one because
he addressed Ireland and he addressed
people that have children I do not even
show children but I think I was shared
myself and my history with others so if
I can conclude with discipline from Pope
John Paul the second keep in contact
with your roots in the soil of your
heritage with your families in your
culture keep true to the faith to the
prayers and values you want only a
common heritage to your children and
erupt through this rich English thank
you very much
[Music]